[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the missing word in this Irish saying: ______ is the poor mans doctor.?", "correct_answer": "Death", "incorrect_answers": ["An apple", "Socialism", "Over-the-counter medication"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Virus fossils from several thousand years ago show what about the origin of viruses?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They were once small cells that lived parasitically on bigger ones.", "They appeared and evolved simultaneously with life on Earth.", "They evolved from bits of DNA that escaped from cells of organisms."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This form of traditional Japanese theater, which aims to make the audience laugh, is characterised by brief plays, stock characters and exaggerated dialogue.", "correct_answer": "Kyogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Kabuki", "Lo fat", "Noh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Frogs can breathe underwater.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The heaviest parrot species on the planet is the Kakapo. What is the average weight that a normal mature Kakapo can reach?", "correct_answer": "2 to 4 kg", "incorrect_answers": ["1.5 to 2 kg", "2.5 to 3 kg", "2 to 2.5 kg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2006 movie starring Sissy Spacek, Donald Sutherland and James DArcy was based on actual events.", "correct_answer": "An American Haunting", "incorrect_answers": ["Dark Waters", "The Grudge", "Amytiville Horror V"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Disney film does the following exchange take place:\nI want to do something for her... but what? \nWell, theres the usual things: flowers... chocolates... promises you dont intend to keep... ?", "correct_answer": "Beauty and the Beast", "incorrect_answers": ["The Black Cauldron", "Lady and the Tramp", "Sleeping Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the point where an objects orbit passes through the plane of Earths orbit.", "correct_answer": "Node", "incorrect_answers": ["Apogee", "Prominence", "Perigee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the traditional Japanese meal Soki?", "correct_answer": "Pork", "incorrect_answers": ["Beef", "Fish", "Chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How was the Genie set free in the Disney film Aladdin?", "correct_answer": "Aladdin freed him with his final wish.", "incorrect_answers": ["He made Aladdin wish him free.", "He ran away.", "Jafar set him free."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Were going to need a bigger boat is a line delivered in what thriller?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["The Perfect Storm", "Speed 2 Cruise Control", "Boat Trip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The film Team America: World Police starts in what country?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Germany", "Russia"]}]